{
    "id": "d46fce8652d54cbaa0348b9bad5cb7d0",
    "title": "Coordinating Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is …………………………… intelligent ……………………….. hard working.",
            "description": "Either could be used here with totally different meanings. ",
            "answers": [
                "neither, nor",
                "both, and",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "12a16a22f65e4440b7d7b9494b95bfea"
        },
        {
            "question": "They need ……………………………. food ………………………… shelter.",
            "description": "The correct options are both...and... and not only...but also....",
            "answers": [
                "both, and",
                "not only, but also",
                "not only, as well as",
                "both, as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "af01aeee6dc548118ea67a9b8a15a26d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She works hard ………………………….. she is struggling to make ends meet.",
            "description": "Yet is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "so",
                "yet"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "54836cd306ee4ae3b2d6192b3bf79732"
        },
        {
            "question": "I want ……………………….. this ………………………. that",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either, or",
                "neither, nor",
                "both, as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6921d07b2a044e79841b6b62dfe78fac"
        },
        {
            "question": "He got up …………………………… rushed towards the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "then",
                "and"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "48dfb5e11b0846fa9788c6f8af4a154a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I tried my best ………………………… I could not solve the puzzle.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "yet",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e1bfbb295acc414b9d8c1919e2d8a0fd"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was the most deserving candidate …………………………… she got the job.",
            "description": "And is not wrong here. So is more correct.",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "so",
                "so that"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5e4da4a5036349ae9ffb5b66c595fc8d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t like cricket, ………………………… does my husband.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "and",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "41cdd7233d194d469f875274da6d1b68"
        },
        {
            "question": "Not a man …………………………. a boy was spared.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nor",
                "and",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9c1f2c9edf5c4ab6aea7acb642fb90a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She seemed ……………………….. surprised …………………………. worried.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both, as well",
                "neither, nor",
                "neither, or"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4e5cadfb9b2e439d9f7fca094ec02e1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………………….  a rogue or a lunatic.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "neither",
                "either",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a4922d3b42bc48e58685b229e5467e06"
        },
        {
            "question": "They will win ................................... they are well trained.",
            "description": "For can mean because in a formal or literary style.",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "for",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1d6a94f32e664c9c8119c87968cb40a6"
        }
    ]
}